l'm

Dede Saputra (Putra)

Student of Esa Unggul University



🚣 Resume



About Me



I am a student at Esa Unggul University majoring in Business Accounting. Besides that, I have worked at PT Sumber Griya Sejahtera for four years. I also have experience handling several clients in the property, accounting, finance, and marketing sectors.

Hire Me

Taxation	85%
Accuracy	90%

Accounting	90%
Marketing	85%

Education

• 01-Jun-2000 to 31-Jun-2006

Primary School

My elementary school is at SDN 012 Jakarta, I graduated in 2006.

01-Jul-2006 *to* 31-Jun-2009

Junior High School

My junior high school is at SMPN 14 Tangerang, I graduated 2009.

High School

My high school is at Pustek Serpong, I graduated in 2012.

Bachelor Degree

I am still studying for a bachelor's degree, academic year 2020 at Esa Unggul University.

Experience

14-Aug-2012 to 14-Aug-2016

Retail

Airport Soekarno-Hatta, Jakarta

Supervisor

I worked for the retail company PT Batik Keris for four years as a Supervisor.

08-Nov-2017 to 08-Nov-2018

Retail

Alam Sutera, Tangerang

Senior Sales Executive

I worked at the retail company PT Kawan Lama Group for one year as a Senior Sales Executive.

01-Oct-2016 to 01-Oct-2017

Retail

Airport Soekarno-Hatta, Jakarta

Senior Sales Executive

I worked in a retail company at PT Tas Center Cemerlang for one year as a Senior Sales Executive.

18-Nov-2018 to Until Now

Services

Kota Cassablanka, Jakarta

Accountants and Finance

I work at the service company PT Sumber Griya Sejahtera. I am an accountant and finance.

Service



Taxation

Provide tax consultation and education to clients. And calculate the amount of tax that needs to be paid by taxpayers to the state.



Finance

Controlling financial activities and transactions, checking related transactions and company financial reports.



Accounting

A process of recording, classifying, summarizing, managing, and presenting data, transactions and events related to finance.



Marketing

Marketing activities or promotion of a brand or brand of products or services carried out through digital media.

Portfolio

ALL TAXATION ACCOUNTING MARKETING





Review

Very professional work, friendly and very independent person. I always use his services for my personal tax purposes.

I work in a retail comparteam. To me he is a ver



Client Na Hafizh



Client Name Fanny

Contact

- Dede Saputra (Putra)
- Accountants and Finance
- putrasaputra.ptsgs@gmail.com
- **+62-813-7005-1699**
- Apartemen Green Park View, West Jakarta, Indonesia















Nama

Nama Anda

Alamat Email

email@gmail.com

Nomor WhatsApp (Optional)

+628

Pesan

Ketik pesan disini...

Kirim Pesan